# MIN LWIN KYAW

Karabük, Turkey · +905524716379 me@minlwinkyaw.com · GitHub · Website · LinkedIn

I am a Computer Engineer and a Software Developer from Myanmar based in Turkey. I have serious passion for designing and creating beautiful websites and mobile applications. I specialize in creating static websites, web applications and mobile applications with secure, fast, and reliable features.

## **SKILLS**

#### **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES**

Python, PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C, C++, C#, MATLAB, Java, Dart

#### **TECHNOLOGIES**

Django, Flask, Symfony, MVC Framework, jQuery, Node.js, Express.js, Flutter, Bootstrap, Materialize and other front-end and JavaScript frameworks

#### **FIELDS**

Image Processing, Networking, Network Security

#### **OTHERS**

Version Control, Windows, Linux, Collaboration

#### **LANGUAGES**

Burmese (Native), English, Turkish

## **EDUCATION**

FEB 2017 – JUN 2020

## **COMPUTER ENGINEERING, KARABUK UNIVERSITY (GPA: 3.55/4.00)**

Studied mainly computer programming and electrical electronic in my major. But specialized in software development. Courses in data structure, algorithm, programming languages, computer architecture, operating system, database, project management, team collaboration and many other covering important components of theory, abstraction, and design.

FEB 2019 - JUN 2019

## INFORMATION SYSTEMS AND ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING,

VILNIUS GEDIMINAS TECHICAL UNIVERSITY (GPA: 9.67/10.00)

Studied there as an Erasmus student for 5 months. Mainly focus on Networking and Network Security. Courses in network security, networking, software engineering, computer architecture.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**2018 - PRESENT** 

#### **FREELANCER**

Being working as freelancer. Created, developed, and deployed website and web application for clients.

**JULY 2019 – AUGUST 2019** 

## **INTERN, TRIOWORX**

Worked as an intern and done one project in two different platform for company. Worked on automatic document scanner and data reader as web application and cross-platform using python, Django, OpenCV, Image Processing, Machine Learning, and some other technologies and framework.

## **PROJECTS**

#### 2019 OCT - 2020 JUNE

#### TRANSPORTATION MANAGEMENT SYSTEM (FINAL YEAR PROJECT)

#### <u>Link | Figma</u>

It is mobile application and web application. It is a transportation management system for more than one country and city. Main features are allowed transportation owners or government to add, create, update their transportation lines or new transportations to our system and that will deliver to user. Users will use our application track transportation, check schedule and transportation routes and finding the best way to go one place to destination by using our real-time multi edges time base graph algorithm. Project was done by using python, Django, and flutter

## 2020 APRIL - 2020 MAY

#### MMCOVID-19 TRACKER MOBILE APPLICATION

#### Back-End | Application

It is a mobile application to track Myanmar's COVID-19 cases in real-time using flutter for mobile application and php and SQL for back-end. Main features for mobile are real-time case tracking, viewing news, checking case and news, and data visualization. Back-end is for data maintenance data and providing other users to publish and updating cases, creating MMCOVID-19 case API for free.

#### 2019 OCT - 2019 DEC

## ONLINE RESTAURANT ORDER

## Link | GitHub

It is a web application restaurant owner to publish their foods, drinks, desserts, and others food related things on their website and allow user to order these foods and drink by using my website. Included CMS for customers and restaurant's owners. Project was done by using Symfony, php, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for Computer Special Topic 1 Course.

2020 FEB - 2020 MAR

JOB POSTING WEBSITE

Link | GitHub

It is a web application for posting jobs and allow people who are looking for job to apply. Included CMS for client and developer in project. Project was done by using Django, python, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for Computer Special Topic 2 Course.

#### 2019 MAY - 2019 JUNE

BRAIN TEASER(GAME)

## Link | Play Store

An offline Math base game. Players can solve brain teasing riddle question using beautiful UI design mobile game. Project was done by using Unity Engine and all the questions were done in Adobe Photoshop.

#### 2019 FEB - 2019 MAY

DOTS AND BOXES (GAME)

#### <u>Link | Play Store</u>

An online multi-player mobile game to play old classic dots and boxes game. Project was done by using Unity Engine, cloud functions using node.js and firebase real-time database.

#### 2020 MAY - 2020 MAY

STEGANOGRAPHY FOR IMAGES

#### Link | GitHub

A cross-platform application to hide one small image to another big image to by using bit level data encryption or password base encryption on bit level encrypted image. Project was done by using python, and image processing.

#### 2018 DEC - 2018 DEC

#### MOUSE CONTROLLER BY COLOR SEGMENTATION

#### Link | OneDrive Link

A cross-platform application control mouse and mouse click by using hand gesture with color segmentation. In program user can move, left click, right click, double click, and dragging without using mouse. Project was done by using python, and OpenCV.

## 2019 DEC - 2020 FEB

## PHOTO SHARING PLATFORM

#### Link | GitHub

It is a web publish or share post or blog with customizable content for users. There are two different section for users, one is for normal users and another one is for admin. Included CMS for normal users and admin. Normal user can create and publish blog and post, like, comment and report other people post and comment on same platform and admin can do all the same things and management all the post from super CMS system. Project was done by using Symfony, php, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for Computer Special Topic 1 Course (Extra).

## 2018 - 2019

#### **WEBSITES**

#### Link

I created some static website while studying HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Find all them on my website.

- Personal Profile Website (2018)
- Product Card Design
- Font Awesome Home Page Folder Clone

- 3 different loading and spinner
- ProgrammingMM Website (website where I used to publish programming course videos)

## **UI/UX PROJECTS**

#### 2020 APRIL - 2020 APRIL

## MMCOVID-19 TRACKER MOBILE APPLICATION DESIGN

#### Link

UI/UX design for MMCOVID-19 Tracking mobile application that was published in 2020 April.

#### 2019 OCT - 2020 JUNE

## TRANSPORTATION MANAGEMENT SYSTEM DESIGN

#### Link

UI/UX design for Transportation Management System (Final Year Project) mobile application.

#### 2018

## OTHER UI/UX DESIGNS

#### Link

List of UI design published on **Dribbble**.

- <u>To-Do List Design</u>
- Mobile Music Player Design